Hello friends, my name
is Gaurav and my channel's name is Prince Chadhta.
Friends, you have listened to the bill. The
name of the company you have chosen today is
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company, it is a long-distance horse. This is the
stock of Swaraj Tractor. Amway, the
insurance sector in India is very deeply penetrated.
Earlier also, I had
made a video on the insurance sector. HDFC Life
friends, this is an Indian company which is a
long-distance horse. Right now, there are a lot of
companies in the insurance sector in India. Very few people have done it. Stay healthy.
As the growth story of India will increase, just
like there is guru ghee in India, similarly there is
also a stop in the sugar sector.
If you compare it with pole vault, then there is nothing in
insurance in India.
And these companies, these are the
companies of India, their rental
houses are subsidiary companies of ICICI
Bank. We can believe in the print roll of ICC Bank, we can believe in
their growth, we
can believe in their business plan. This is a privately
managed company. Friends,
if we play the game for a long distance,
Friends, if we want to earn money in the stock market, then
we will have to play the long game.
I have already said this in many of my videos
that if we want to earn money in the stock market, then
we will have to play the game in the long term.
We will have to do compounding.
We will have to buy such stocks which are
long race horses. Recently, I have
told you about such stocks on my channel. I have told you about such
stocks whose fundamentals are
not wealth creators. All the
stocks which are wealth creators, fundamentals are
strong stocks. Friends, there is
no debt in any of them. This is one of them.
ICICI Lombard is the best place for you to choose. There is going to be a
lot of growth in the general insurance sector. If
you want to play the long game in the stock market, at
least for the tennis game, then you have to include this
sector in your portfolio. If
you tell me about yours personally, then I have
two
stocks of the insurance sector in my portfolio.
One of them is HDFC Life and the other is
ICICI Lombard, apart from this SBI
Life, ICICI Prudential Life, friends, it is also
very good
that you choose any one of these four and
keep them in your portfolio,
play the long term game with them, you will get
good returns from them, there will be capital appreciation, it will be
wealth creator, as the
value of insurance increases in India, people will become
aware regarding their health insurance, regarding
their term insurance, regarding
their vehicle insurance
and many other types of situations,
as friends, people will get
insurance in these sectors, there will be a lot of growth in these companies, the
profit of growth in these will increase, there will be capital appreciation, it will be
wealth creator, you will
get good dividend, play the long term game
friends, we should buy them without any rules and after buying
we should forget that we have any
such stocks, right now if we feel that
these stocks are doing very well, that the
GP is increasing very well, their PI is
not increasing much, then gradually we can increase
our investment in these stocks.  I will increase it.
Frankly speaking, right now I have
1% long ICC and 1% long
HDFC Life in my portfolio. I will see from time to time
in one year, two years, three years, how
their stock price is
increasing. If good results come,
profits will increase, prices will increase, that will increase, there will be
compounding, so I will gradually
increase my holding. Then I will keep
telling you about it on my channel also.
In these stocks, see
friends, you must have seen that I have shown you all the
strong stocks. This is also a gem stock, a
favorite of the market, it is a very good
printer of that. We
can click on this sector. This
sector is great to have our depot open.
ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company Limited is one of the leading
private sector general insurance companies in
India with a gross return premium of ₹
147,981,000 for the year end
March 31, 2019. D-Company 0.65 million poles
and settled 1.6 million Muslims 3125 and
company. I also have a  When I got frustrated, I took it
1 inch and put ice in it and I told two
professors what have they done that they have ruined
my life, you have to pay premium for 20 years, you will get
hurt for 20 years, Rs. 5000 in 20 years, right now
I am calling the bank helpline and asking that
if I had bought their daughter, they are
charging such a huge penalty that
I am not getting even the return of the money from you,
if I vote for them in a Twenty20 match, then
I will get center time on the alarm set, so
thinking this, I am
noting this, so this is an affair
friends, what I mean to say is that they
play a long game like LIC people say that once a
customer comes, keep him for 10 years, 20 years
and you will keep
paying the premium, they had profits and
friends, what do they have to give you,
if you and any insurance company
take an insurance plan from them for your body, then in that you have to
give 68 percent time and
its minimum stark, friends, you have to give
1517  If the center minimum health
goes well then fifty
internal will run well and will give it to 3242 center and
friends where have I sent you, the
Samagam Pandey is happening at a higher rate than the net
and where is 3241 friends if there is round compounding of 50% then
your money will double by 30
friends these are very good stories have
wealth creators stories you have to keep them
in your cupboard market that
you are its then pyro current price
of the team is weak 52-week high 1400 ground
and 52-week low 805 book value of it 132 have to keep
fifty-six and the back of the industry
right now on which thing you
cannot get on this MP in the coming 3 years
that stock script is very good it can be
purchased CMP and overseas
see its 23k road and allegations from its 16k road
friend at free companies there is
no debt on the company the business of the company has a very good growth story  The
model is very good, from the debt-equity
ratio point of view, its land is very good,
its profit growth is 60%, how is it,
Reliance company has 55101
and you can invest in this roti 6 10 face value
stocks 20 sainik nodal point for nine
percent, this is a
very good figure friends, my uniform is my
favorite song, we have to play this sector, do a
little, do more
but play the long distance game, take it and
see this friends,
in its peer comparison, stock like HDFC Life
SBI Life ICICI Lombard ICSE
Pre Live Jan 09
Junoon 1600, leave that out friends,
apart from this, out of the first four companies,
you must have minimum two companies in your report, that is the growth
story of India's growth,
Prince on Sony, earlier I
told you, speaking in my purse, in these
you can keep your personal, in HDFC Life and
ICSE and Barmer personally, folded
fans in these and I till distance
Friends, play the long-range game, see its balance sheet,
you will enjoy it, see its fundamentals, by
looking at its results, its turnover in June 2017
was around 120 crores, which is its current
result, it is a very good result, friends, the
market has been closed since 08 2012 due to the last date, the
business of the company has been closed due to the last date, still there is
growth in their sales because they
nurtured Pranina and they are looking at the
premium look of their online policy,
see its balance sheet in March 2018,
right after 2016, it is 28 to 1000, so now when
these people will open their new
policy, when more people will become aware, more
awareness will come among the people that we have more
health insurance, regarding the
business that comes in the insurance sector, then
these will be the companies which will lead the
insurance sector,
friends, definitely make an appointment in SBI Life, ICICI Prudential and HDFC Life,
friends, see the net profit of 210 team,
all-rounder June  In 2017, which kept increasing, this
time it came to 282 crores and in March 2019, it
gave 228 crores and 212 crores.
Friends, its GPS is gradually increasing, the
net profit is increasing, the products of the company are also increasing and
what do you think, this is a
private sector company, this printer is very
good, its share holding pattern is very good,
it has some whiskey technique, it has a good meter
front holding, it has holding of this chilli powder
and in f4 message, they have
also declared this company very well,
see that from its co-owner, friends, do
not get goosebumps of 307 20%, set the time
and the compound profit growth was this
time in the 16th and 0 0 4 crumbs and
see senior, in one year it gave 14%, it has given more,
it has been listed for a long time, friends,
only we can purchase it as CMD, take it and
fold it, friends, frankly speaking,
I have also added it for a very good bonding,
see the return on equity scheme, it is 60%, agree with it.
Send friends, a very good
source of India's growth story stock,
friends, if you want to do health rate on this, then
in stock market, I have told
in every video of mine that the best way to create wealth in stock market is to take
good stocks, good stocks, fundamentally
strong stocks and hold them,
build your portfolio
slowly and gradually
invest in them only, do MS in available stocks also,
waste only below,
use them more while turning on battery saver mode,
friends, in my channel, I have given you all the
stocks of different sectors, 335,
and after taking out a useful gem talk,
I have told you about any such stock
whose fundamentals are also good and which is wealth
creator, then stop, there are many other
good games like zinc dros, people like IDCA have
handed over the power to everyone,
friends, it has not even doubled the money in 10 years,
what is the benefit of investing in such stocks, so give vote, add the one which has
customers, add the one whose back value
number, whose GPS is increasing, due to which it is safe  I am showing you all the stocks in
which you are making profit,
pick such stocks, capital
application will be up in them, I have shown you
all the stocks in my channel Wealth Creator
friends, pick good strokes from these,
invest only in the market
and hold it for a long time, I
told you this in the last video friends,
20 30 40 50 seconds, if you are not playing the game then
you should not invest in stock market, you
should invest in mutual funds and only invest in it,
if you are coming to stock market and making
desktop purchases then at
least think that we have played the game of 100 per cent for
10 years, if you
play then you will earn 10 lakhs, then
those cigarettes will be for you,
for your children, you should set a goal
and for the long game you have to enter the market,
friends these are the
friends of the market, the market never
goes in a quadrant, neither does it
go in attraction downwards nor does it get
extraction upwards, it gradually goes up and down up and
down if this is the volatility
of the market  There is a friend and those who understood this volatility and
made it their friend, they have
earned a lot of money in the stock market and will continue to earn. The
stock market tests your friends' patience.
In the stock market, Mr.
Warren Buffett takes the name of the world's most renowned person in every video.
He is our guru, our
goal. For example, I will
not take the name of withdrawal in any video. Friends, that connection, that
Disney has become useless.
Mr. Warren Buffett says that
money in the market is made by an impatient person,
after which the more patient people
go to Siddh Rahman. Means,
in whichever question the paste of holding is
needed, only the one who has patience makes money. His
friend at Charging Charlie, but he
says that I told you in the last video that
money which is a wealth creator is a marathon, it is
not soft, it is a drop test match, it is
in Twenty20 or
T20, if you play then you will not be able to earn money,
if you play slowly like a test match,
slowly with patience, we
stay in the market, we do not let our wickets
fall, then in the market  Money will definitely
increase friends, the market forces that
want downward movement in the market are
temporary and the
upward movement of the market due to the ball of the market is for permanent,
I was just telling you Mr. Breakup,
well Charlie Temple once said that
as I told you that a marathon race is
not printed, he is saying that the real
money is not in selling and purchasing,
real money is not in selling, but in purchasing,
best of all real money is in waiting, how was your hold
request and you have
chosen your stock in such a way, if you have
chosen the stock in such a way that its life is
not 10 years in which there will be no lumps,
like I just told you about ITC,
now like L&T friends, which is India
's largest infrastructure company,
fundamentals are good, it is a very good
company, it means it is a very good company,
but still it is not a great stock,
if you want to create a bank then you will have to
pick a company like Bajaj Finance in profit, you will have to pick Burger Paints, you will have to
pick less on Avni Super Mario, you will have to
pick HDFC Bank  You will have to do this,
you will have to pick such companies, Gym
Wealth Creator of Friends, if you liked my
video, you liked what I said, then
like my video,
subscribe to my channel, Friends,
if anyone wants point service, then WhatsApp me on the number given below,
for portfolio service, we will chat among ourselves and I will
call you, after the call, I will
give you a very good business flip read,
friends, and I will try my best to ensure that
you get those cigarettes in the coming time,
Hello Friends, see you in the next video,
Stay Healthy, Stay Home, Stay Healthy, Thank you
Friends, you will get it, Thank you